Sounds: Kingdom Animalia
Podcasts Sting;
Opening Theme;
Animalia Electro Guitar begins
Devon: Hello podcast listeners.
It’s me, Devon, with some
updates. This is not a full
episode, but I am here to say
episode 13 is on the way. I just
finished recording and am
working on editing it as you
listen.
But there is more to be excited
for. Episode 13 is our late
April Fools episode. Those who
have been listening to our show
since Spring 2023 will know that
in our April Fools episode we
talk about 5 crazy animals, 4
real, 1 I just made up, and you
can send in your guesses of
which it is. But this time I’m
raising the stakes—if you win
you get your very own…
Sounds: Drumroll
Devon: 3D-printed set of Chet
and Cap models!
Sounds: Ta-Da!
Devon: Yes, you get two guesses,
and if you guess the fake animal
correctly, you can win your very
own set of Chet and Cap models.
Photos will be on the episode
page for episode 13 when it
releases.
So keep your ears out, and until
then, keep exploring this
amazing Kingdom… Animalia. Bye!